<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Factions>
	<Faction id="emissary_company"
			 initial_posX="134.52"
			 initial_posY="498.12"
			 banner_key="27.116.83.1849.1850.764.764.1.0.-46.419.116.116.770.770.764.764.1.1.-47"
             culture="Culture.vlandia"
             default_party_template="PartyTemplate.emissary_party_template"
			 settlement_banner_mesh="encounter_flag_f"
			 is_minor_faction="true"
			 is_clan_type_mercenary="true"
             name="Легион Наёмных Крестоносцев (6 Крестоносцы)"
             tier="6"
             text="Eric Maklite, known among the ranks and across the lands as the Red Baron's Emissary, weaves a tale as enigmatic as it is formidable. Born under the harsh, unforgiving sun of the Zexen Alliance Highlands, Eric's early years were steeped in the kind of adversity that molds the unbreakable. The youngest of five siblings, he learned quickly to fend for himself, his keen intellect and unmatched dexterity setting him apart from his peers.
The Red Baron, intrigued by the young prodigy's potential, took Eric under his wing, offering him a place in his elite guard. Under the Baron's tutelage, Eric's natural leadership abilities were honed to perfection, his strategic mind sharpened to think several moves ahead of any adversary. He quickly rose through the ranks, his loyalty and successes in various skirmishes earning him the title of the Red Baron's Emissary While sailing through the central ocean, his ship was caught in a maelstrom and is transported to Calradia. The Emissary continues his work in the name of the Baron in these strange lands..
As the emissary, Eric became the voice and the arm of the Red Baron, negotiating contracts with kings and warlords, his name synonymous with the inevitable success of their missions."
			 owner="Hero.spc_emissary_leader_object">
		<!--
           label_color="000000"
           color="000000"
           color2="000000"
           alternative_color="000000"
           alternative_color2="000000"
		   -->
		<minor_faction_character_templates>
			<template id="NPCCharacter.spc_emissary_leader_0" />
			<template id="NPCCharacter.spc_emissary_leader_1" />
			<template id="NPCCharacter.spc_emissary_leader_2" />
			<template id="NPCCharacter.spc_emissary_leader_3" />
		</minor_faction_character_templates>
	</Faction>
</Factions>
